

VICKY MAHFUDY

Data Analyst / Business Intelligence

+6282299168877



vickymahfudy@gmail.com 💟



linkedin.com/in/vickymahfudy in



github.com/vickymahfudy



public.tableau.com/app/profile/vicky.mahfudy



SUMMARY:

Data analyst with strong interest in data industry. Experienced with Spreadsheet, SQL, and Python on data processing and analysis. Also experienced with data visualization tools like Tableau and Google Data Studio. Currently building several skill sets in prepare to become a data scientist. Very confident to work by passion and constantly develop more skills.

SPECIALIZATIONS:

SQL, Python, R, Excel, Spreadsheet, Tableau, Google Data Studio

Technical Skills:

Data ETL, Data Cleaning and Manipulation, Exploratory Data Analysis, Data Visualization, Data Clustering

Soft Skills:

Public Speaking, Leadership, Analytical Thinking, Creative Thinking

Language:

English (Limited working proficiency), Bahasa Indonesia

CERTIFICATES:

FULL STACK DATA ANALYTICS

RevoU

Link: intip.in/FSDARevou

DATA ANALYST PROFESSIONAL ACADEMY Digital Talent Scholarship

BUSINESS INTELLIGENCE SHORT COURSE

Rakamin Academy Link: intip.in/BIRakamin

Link: intip.in/DAPROA

DATA ANALYSIS INTENSIVE BOOTCAMP

MySkill

Link: intip.in/DAMySkill

WORK EXPERIENCE:

TEAM LEAD FULL STACK DATA ANALYTICS

RevoU (Part-time) August 2022 - Present

- Assist instructors in teaching students about data analytics and tools required by Data Analyst
- Assisting the group of 12 students in understanding the materials of the Data Analytics process during the lecture.
- Grading and reporting the student's attendance and their assignments.

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

Institut Teknologi Sepuluh Nopember (Full-time) November 2019 - August 2022

Build and maintain 3 web-based information system for Bidang Perencanaan, Keuangan, dan Sarana Prasarana:

- Application for analyzing data of new students.
- Application for monitoring data of revenue system.
- Application for processing finance operational.

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY:

REVOU

Full Stack Data Analytics May 2022 - August 2022

Skills:

- Dissect some metrics and data attributes of the customer journey in apps.
- Create an EDA, statistical measurement, and do A/B testing with t-test approach using Google Spreadsheet.
- Use SQL to extract, transform, load, manipulate, and analyze the data stored in a database and generate cohort analysis.
- Create customer segmentation using RFM analysis and K-Means analysis using Python.
- Create advanced interactive dashboard with Tableau.

Achievements:

- Being the Best Student among 60 students in the class.
- First Winner of Group Final Project among the other 18 groups.

INSTITUT TEKNOLOGI SEPULUH NOPEMBER

Bachelor's Degree in Informatics

2015 - 2019

Cumulative GPA: 3.56/4.00

PROJECT:

IBM HR ANALYTICS - ATTRITION ANALYSIS AND PREDICTION

RevoU

Tools: Spreadsheet, Python, and Tableau

This project was done for the Final Group Project at RevoU. We performed end-to-end data analysis and Logistic Regression to predict attrition rate. Our regression model and recommendations successfully predicted a decrease in attrition rate from 16% to 11%.

Link: intip.in/GFPGroupG

COVID-19 GLOBAL VACCINATIONS PROGRESS DASHBOARD

RevoU

Tools: Tableau

This project is an advanced assignment from Data Visualization week in the FSDA program at RevoU. Where we are asked to create a dashboard of Covid-19 Global Vaccinations Progress using Tableau.

Link: intip.in/AdvAssignmentTableau/

RFM ANALYSIS AND CLUSTER ANALYSIS

Revoll

Tools: Python

Create RFM Clustering for segmenting customer based on their recency, frequency, and monetary. Also create state cluster based on their customer behavior using K-means Clustering.

Link: github.com/vickymahfudy/E-commerce_RFM_Clustering

PORTFOLIO: intip.in/PortoVicky